export const questionWords = [
  {
    question: "wer",
    answer: "who",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wer hat mein Buch genommen?",
    sampleEnglish: "Who took my book?"
  },
  {
    question: "was",
    answer: "what",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Was machst du heute?",
    sampleEnglish: "What are you doing today?"
  },
  {
    question: "wo",
    answer: "where",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wo wohnst du?",
    sampleEnglish: "Where do you live?"
  },
  {
    question: "wohin",
    answer: "where to",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wohin gehst du?",
    sampleEnglish: "Where are you going to?"
  },
  {
    question: "woher",
    answer: "where from",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Woher kommst du?",
    sampleEnglish: "Where do you come from?"
  },
  {
    question: "wann",
    answer: "when",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wann beginnt der Film?",
    sampleEnglish: "When does the movie start?"
  },
  {
    question: "warum",
    answer: "why",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Warum bist du traurig?",
    sampleEnglish: "Why are you sad?"
  },
  {
    question: "wie",
    answer: "how",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wie geht es dir?",
    sampleEnglish: "How are you?"
  },
  {
    question: "wie viel",
    answer: "how much",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wie viel kostet das?",
    sampleEnglish: "How much does this cost?"
  },
  {
    question: "wie viele",
    answer: "how many",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Wie viele Personen kommen zur Party?",
    sampleEnglish: "How many people are coming to the party?"
  },
  {
    question: "welcher / welche / welches",
    answer: "which",
    category: "Question Words",
    sampleGerman: "Welches Buch m√∂chtest du lesen?",
    sampleEnglish: "Which book would you like to read?"
  }
]; 